let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What was Meta Platforms Inc formerly known as?",
        answer: "Facebook",
        options: [
            "Instagram",
            "Facebook",
            "whatsapp"
        ]

    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which English city is known as the Steel City?",
        answer: "Sheffield",
        options: [
            "Mumbai",
            "Austin",
            "Sheffield"
        ]

    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which former British colony was given back to China in 1997?",
        answer: "Hong Kong",
        options: [
            "Taiwan",
            "Hong Kong",
            "Xinjiang"
        ]

    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Haematology is the study of what?",
        answer: "The blood",
        options: [
            "The tissue",
            "The cell",
            "The blood"
        ]

    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is the main ingredient in guacamole?",
        answer: "Avocado",
        options: [
            "Avocado",
            "Apple",
            "Pineapple"
        ]

    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Rojo is the Spanish word for which colour?",
        answer: "Red",
        options: [
            "Yellow",
            "Red",
            "Blue"
        ]

    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which is the only planet in our solar system not named after a Roman or Greek god?",
        answer: "Earth",
        options: [
            "Jupiter",
            "Mercury",
            "Earth"
        ]

    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "In which sport is the Davis Cup contested?",
        answer: "Tennis",
        options: [
            "Badminton",
            "Glof",
            "Tennis"
        ]

    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "How many wisdom teeth does the average adult have?",
        answer: "Four",
        options: [
            "Five",
            "Four",
            "Eight"
        ]

    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "How many lives is a cat said to have?",
        answer: "9",
        options: [
            "7",
            "9",
            "4"
        ]

    },
];